const CardData = {
    VPVR: [
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Anime",
            answer: "Monogatari Series",
            rarity: "Rare",
            icon: "Tv",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Animal",
            answer: "Narwhal",
            rarity: "Rare",
            icon: "Fish"
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Dessert",
            answer: "Donut",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Donut"
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Programming Language",
            answer: "JavaScript",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Code"
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Fruit",
            answer: "Apple",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Apple"
        }
    ],
    Colorezz: [
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Pokemon",
            answer: "Samurott",
            rarity: "Rare",
            icon: "Droplet",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite FPS Game",
            answer: "Overwatch",
            rarity: "Epic",
            icon: "Crosshair",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Artstyle",
            answer: "Cel Shaded",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Palette",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Energy Drink",
            answer: "Zoa",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Zap",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Song",
            answer: "Lovers Rock",
            rarity: "Epic",
            icon: "Music",
        }
    ],
    Selva: [
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Historical Figure",
            answer: "LeBron James",
            rarity: "Rare",
            icon: "Crown",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Fast Food",
            answer: "Angry Chickz",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Drumstick",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Console",
            answer: "Ps4",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "GamepadDirectional",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Exercise",
            answer: "Endless Walking",
            rarity: "Common",
            icon: "Footprints",
        },
        {
            prompt: "Favorite Movie",
            answer: "Goodwill Hunting",
            rarity: "Epic",
            icon: "Clapperboard",
        }

    ]

}


export default CardData